Beveridge Collection of Unemployment, Volumes 1-20 on Microfilm 6130 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Unemployment, etc., 1890-1914. V.4. (Reel 3)
  - V.4-41. Les premiers resultats de la nouvelle loi anglaise d'assurance sociale, 1903; 42 (Reel 3)
    Bellom (Maurice): Les premiers resultats de la nouvelle loi anglaise d'assurance sociale. II. Assurance contre le chomage. (Journal des Economistes. September 1903)
  - V.4-42. The Christ of dogma and of experience, 1905; 43 (Reel 3)
    Pickard -Cambridge (W.A.). The Christ of dogma and of experience. (The Hibbert Journal, January 1905).
- Unemployed, Poor Law, etc., 1893-1905. V.5. (Reel 4)
  - V.5-1. Report on agencies and methods for dealing with the unemployed, 1893; 1 (Reel 4)
    United Kingdom. Board of Trade: Labour Department. Report on agencies and methods for dealing with the unemployed. 1893.
  - V.5-2. Map to accompany report on agencies and methods for dealing with the unemployed, 1893; 2 (Reel 4)
    United Kingdom. Board of Trade: Labour Department. Map to accompany report on agencies and methods for dealing with the unemployed. 1893.
  - V.5-3. Poor Law Commissioners' report, 1834-1905; 3 (Reel 4)
    United Kingdom. Poor Law Commissioners' report of 1834. Copy of the report made in 1834 by the Commissioners for inquiring into the administration and practical operation of the Poor Laws. 1905.
  - V.5-4. Report by the chief labour correspondence of the Board of Trade on Trade Unions, 1892-1900; 4 (Reel 4)
    United Kingdom. Board of Trade (Labour Department). Report by the chief labour correspondence of the Board of Trade on Trade Unions in 1899, with comparative statistics for 1892-1898. 1900.
- Provincial Distress Committees, 1905 Oct.-1909. V.6. (Reel 5)
  - V.6-1. Birkenhead Distress Committee, 1906; 5 (Reel 5)
    Birkenhead, County - Borough of: Birkenhead Distress Committee (Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905). Report, 1906.
  - V.6-2. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 6 (Reel 5)
    Birmingham, City of: Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report upon the proceedings of the Distress Committee from November 1906, to June 1907.
  - V.6-3. Report of the Clerk and Investigation Officer, 1906-1907; 7 (Reel 5)
    Bournemouth, County Borough of: Distress Committee. Report of the Clerk and Investigation Officer, 1906-7.
  - V.6-4. The Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 8 (Reel 5)
    Bristol, City and County of: The Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee for the year ended March 31st, 1907.
  - V.6-5. First Report of the work of the Distress Committee, 1906; 9 (Reel 5)
    Burton-upon-Trent, County Borough of: First Report of the work of the Distress Committee, in conjunction with the Mayor's fund in aid of distress, 1906.
  - V.6-6. Report for twelve weeks ending July 6th, 1907, 10 (Reel 5)
    Coventry, City of: Labour Bureau: Report for twelve weeks ending July 6th, 1907.
  - V.6-7. Report of the secretary of the Distress Committee, 1907; 11 (Reel 5)
    Dudley. Report of the secretary of the Distress Committee ... March 31st, 1907.
  - V.6-8. The second annual report, 1906-1907; 12 (Reel 5)
    East Ham, Borough of: Distress Committee. The second annual report, session 1906-7.
  - V.6-9. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 13 (Reel 5)
    Edinburgh, City of: "Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905." Report by Distress Committee ... from 1st December 1905 to 15th May 1907.
  - V.6-10. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 14 (Reel 5)
    Great Yarmouth, County Borough of: The Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Second annual report of the ... Distress Committee to the General Purposes Committee of the Town Council.
  - V.6-11. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 15 (Reel 5)
    Halifax, County Borough of. The Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Second annual report of the Distress Committee, year ending March 31st, 1907.
  - V.6-12. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 16 (Reel 5)
    Leeds, City of: The Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee for the year ended 31 July 1907.
  - V.6-13. Reports proposed to be presented to the Council, 1907; 17 (Reel 5)
    Leicester, Borough of. Reports proposed to be presented to the Council ... 25th June 1907. Distress Committee.
  - V.6-14. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 18 (Reel 5)
    Liverpool, City of. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Second annual report of the Distress Committee. 1907.
  - V.6-15. Fourth annual report, 1908-1909; 19 (Reel 5)
    Manchester, City of. Fourth annual report of the Distress Committee appointed by the City Council under the provisions of the "Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905." 1908-9.
  - V.6-16. Second annual report, 1907; 20 (Reel 5)
    Newcastle-upon-Tyne, City and County of. Distress Committee ... Second annual report, year ending 30th April, 1907.
  - V.6-17. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 21 (Reel 5)
    Norwich, City and County of. Report of the Distress Committee to the Council upon the work carried out during the past winter, under the provisions of the Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, and the orders of the Local Government Board thereon. 1907.
  - V.6-18. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 22 (Reel 5)
    Nottingham, City of. Report of the Distress Committee ... up to the 31st ... March, 1907.
  - V.6-19. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 23 (Reel 5)
    Plymouth, Borough of. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee to 31st March, 1907.
  - V.6-20. Return relating to the proceedings of the Committee, 1907; 24 (Reel 5)
    Reading. Distress Committee. Return relating to the proceedings of the Committee during the year ended 31st March, 1907.
  - V.6-21. Secretary's second report of the work done, 1907; 25 (Reel 5)
    Sunderland, County Borough of. Distress committee ... Secretary's second report of the work done, September 1906 to September 1907.
  - V.6-22. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 26 (Reel 5)
    Warrington, County Borough of. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of Inquiry Officer to Distress Committee, for the year ended 31st March 1907.
  - V.6-23. First annual report and secretary's general observations, 1906; 27 (Reel 5)
    West Ham, County Borough of. Distress Committee. First annual report and secretary's general observations, October. 1905 - June 1906.
  - V.6-24. Second annual report, 1907; 28 (Reel 5)
    West Ham, County Borough of. Distress Committee. Second annual report, year ending June 30th 1907.
  - V.6-25. Report of Investigation Officer to Distress Committee, 1907; 29 (Reel 5)
    Wolverhampton. Report of Investigation Officer to Distress Committee, 31 July 1907.
- London Unemployed, 1906-1907 (V.7). London Unemployed, 1903-1906 (V.8.) (Reel 6)
  - V.7-1. Unemployed (Workmen) Act, 1905, 1907; 1 (Reel 6)
    Bermondsey, Metropolitan Borough of. Unemployed (Workmen) Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee 1st July 1906 to 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-2. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 2 (Reel 6)
    Bethnal Green. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee year ended 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-3. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 3 (Reel 6)
    Camberwell, Borough. Report of the ... Distress Committee ... May 13th, 1906 - June 30th, 1907.
  - V.7-4. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 4 (Reel 6)
    Chelsea, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee upon the work carried out under the provisions of the Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, and the orders thereon of the Local Government Board, for the year ending 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-5. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 5 (Reel 6)
    London, City of. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee of the Common Council to the Central (Unemployed) Body for London, for the year ended June 30th 1907.
  - V.7-6. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, 1907; 6 (Reel 6)
    Deptford, Metropolitan Borough of. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report of the Distress Committee for the year ended 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-7. Report of Distress Committee, 1906-1907; 7 (Reel 6)
    Finsbury, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee ... 1906-7.
  - V.7-8. Report of Distress Committee, 1907; 8 (Reel 6)
    Fulham, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee ... for the period, 1st July 1906 to 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-9. Report of Distress Committee, 1907; 9 (Reel 6)
    Greenwich, Metropolitan Borough of. Distress Committee ... report, July 1st, 1906 -June 30th, 1907.
  - V.7-10. Report of Distress Committee, 1907; 10 (Reel 6)
    Hackney, Metropolitan Borough of. Distress Committee ... report, July 1st, 1906 to June 30th, 1907.
  - V.7-11. Report of Distress Committee, 1906-1907; 11 (Reel 6)
    Hammersmith, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the ... Distress Committee under the Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. 1906-7.
  - V.7-12. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 12 (Reel 6)
    Hampstead, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee, 1st July 1906 to 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-14. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 13 (Reel 6)
    Lambeth, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee for the year ended June 30th, 1907.
  - V.7-15. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 14 (Reel 6)
    Lewisham, Borough of. Central (Unemployed) Body for London ... Report ... Distress Committee, 1st July 1906 to 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-16. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 15 (Reel 6)
    Paddington, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee ... for the year ended 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-17. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 16 (Reel 6)
    Poplar, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee for the year ending 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-18. Report of the Distress Committee, 1906-1907; 17 (Reel 6)
    Saint Marylebone, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee. 1906-7.
  - V.7-19. Report of the Distress Committee, 1906-1907; 18 (Reel 6)
    Saint Pancras, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee. 1906-7.
  - V.7-20. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 19 (Reel 6)
    Southwark, Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee for the year ended 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-21. Report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 20 (Reel 6)
    Stepney. Report of the Stepney Distress Committee under the Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, from July 1, 1906 to June 30, 1907.
  - V.7-22. Second report of the Distress Committee, 1907; 21 (Reel 6)
    Stoke Newington, Metropolitan Borough of. Second report of the Distress Committee ... for the year ended 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-23. Report of Distress Committee, 1907; 22 (Reel 6)
    Wandsworth, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the ... Distress Committee, from 1st July 1906 to 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-24. Report of Distress Committee, 1907; 23 (Reel 6)
    Westminster, City of. Report of Distress Committee, for the year ended 30th June 1907.
  - V.7-25. Report of Distress Committee, 1907; 24 (Reel 6)
    Woolwich, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee for the year ending 30th June, 1907.
  - V.7-26. Employment exchanges, 1907; 25 (Reel 6)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry). Employment exchanges. 1907.
  - V.7-27. Labour exchanges, 1907; 26 (Reel 6)
    Beveridge (Sir William Henry). Labour exchanges. 1907.
  - V.8-1. Report of Central Executive Committee, 1904-1905; 27 (Reel 6)
    London Unemployed Fund, 1904-5. Report of Central Executive Committee.
  - V.8-2. Report of Executive Committee, 1903-1904; 28 (Reel 6)
    Mansion House Committee on the Unemployed 1903-4. Report of Executive Committee.
  - V.8-3. Report of a temporary colony at Garden City for unemployed workmen, 1905; 29 (Reel 6)
    Oxford: Trinity College Settlement. Report of a temporary colony at Garden City for unemployed workmen, mainly from West Ham, during February, March and April, 1905.
  - V.8-4. Report of the Unemployed Central Committee, 1903-1904; 30 (Reel 6)
    Camberwell, Borough of. Report of the Unemployed Central Committee. 1903-4.
  - V.8-5. Report of the Joint Committee for Bethnal Green, 1904-1905; 31 (Reel 6)
    Bethnal Green. London Unemployed Fund, 1904-1905. Report of the Joint Committee for Bethnal Green.
  - V.8-6. Report of the Unemployed Central Committee, 1904-1905; 32 (Reel 6)
    Camberwell, Borough of. Report of the ... Unemployed Central Committee. 1904-5.
  - V.8-7. Report of the Borough Engineer on the unemployed, 1904-1905; 33 (Reel 6)
    Camberwell, Borough of. Report of the Borough Engineer on the unemployed, 1904-5, with table of statistics.
  - V.8-8. Report of Joint Committee, 1905; 34 (Reel 6)
    Finsbury, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Joint Committee re unemployed, Winter 1904- 1905.
  - V.8-9. Report of Joint Committee, 1904-1905; 35 (Reel 6)
    Poplar, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Joint Committee on the Unemployed on relief work during the winter of 1904-5.
  - V.8-10. Report of Distress Committee, 1905-1906; 36 (Reel 6)
    Chelsea, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee, 1905-6.
  - V.8-12. Report of the Distress Committee, 1906; 37 (Reel 6)
    Southwark, Borough of. Report of the Distress Committee for the period from the date of their constitution to the 30th June 1906.
  - V.8-13. A report upon the work and procedure of the Distress Committees, 1906; 38 (Reel 6)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. A report upon the work and procedure of the Distress Committees in London from their constitution to 30th June 1906.
  - V.8-14. Report of Distress Committee, 1905-1906; 39 (Reel 6)
    Saint Marylebone, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Distress Committee, 1905-6.
  - V.8-15. Report of the Joint Unemployed Committee, 40 (Reel 6)
    Islington, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Joint Unemployed Committee.
  - V.8-16. Report of the Joint Committee of Borough Councillors and Guardians of a census of unemployed, 1905; 41 (Reel 6)
    Hackney, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Joint Committee of Borough Councillors and Guardians of a census of unemployed for the Borough of Hackney, 1904-1905.
  - V.8-17. Report of the Joint Committee, 1904-1905; 42 (Reel 6)
    Paddington, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the Joint Committee re Unemployed, Winter, 1904-5.
  - V.8-18. The unemployed, 1904-1905; 43 (Reel 6)
    Woolwich, Borough of. The unemployed, 1904-5. Report of the ... Joint Unemployed Committee.
  - V.8-19. Unemployed (Workmen) Act, 1905, 1906; 44 (Reel 6)
    Bermondsey, Metropolitan Borough of. Unemployed (Workmen) Act, 1905. Report of the ... Distress Committee, 27th October 1905 to 30th June, 1906.
  - V.8-20. Report of the work of the Distress Committee, 1906; 45 (Reel 6)
    Camberwell, Borough of ... Report of the work of the Distress Committee to 30th June 1906.
  - V.8-21. Report of proceedings of the Committee, 1906; 46 (Reel 6)
    Stepney. Distress Committee. Report of proceedings of the Committee, July 1906.
  - V.8-22. The Unemployed, 1905-1906; 47 (Reel 6)
    Wooliwch, Borough of. The Unemployed, 1905-6. Report of the ... Distress Committee.
  - V.8-23. Report of the Distress Committee, 1906; 48 (Reel 6)
    Wandsworth, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of the ... Distress Committee, 11th October 1905 to 30th June 1906.
- London Unemployed, 1903-1908 (V.9). Vagrancy and Labour Colonies, 1903-1906. (V.10) (Reel 7)
  - V.9-1 Preliminary statement, 1905; 1 (Reel 7)
    United Kingdom. London Unemployed Fund. Preliminary statement (as on the 14th April, 1905), prepared by the request of the President of the Local Government Board by the Central Executive Committee. Cd. 2561
  - V.9-2 Preliminary report, 1906; 2 (Reel 7)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Preliminary report ... to May 12th 1906.
  - V.9-3 Second report, 1906; 3 (Reel 7)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Second report ... from May 12th, 1906 to June 30th, 1907.
  - V.9-4 Third report, 1906-1907; 4 (Reel 7)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Third report ... from 1st July 1907 to 30th June 1909.
  - V.9-5 Minutes of the proceedings at a conference, 1907-1909; 5 (Reel 7)
    London County Council. Lack of employment in London. Minutes of the proceedings at a conference, on 13th February and 3rd April, 1903, between representatives of the London County Council and of the administrative authorities in London, on the subject of the lack of employment in London together with a report of the General Purposes Committee ... with regard to the recommendations made by the Conference.
  - V.10-1 Departmental Committee on Vagrancy, 1906; 6 (Reel 7)
    United Kingdom. Departmental Committee on Vagrancy: Report, 1906. Cd. 2852. Minutes of Evidence, 1906, Cd. 2891. Appendix to the report ... with charts and maps, 1906, Cd. 2892.
  - V.10-2 Report on the Salvation Army Colonies in the United States and at Hadleigh, England, 1905; 7 (Reel 7)
    United Kingdom. Report on the Salvation Army Colonies in the United States and at Hadleigh, England: with scheme of national land settlement, by Commissioner H. Rider Haggard, 1905. Cd. 2562.
  - V.10-3 Report of the Departmental Committee, 1906; 8 (Reel 7)
    United Kingdom. Departmental Committee on Agricultural Settlements in British Colonies. Report of the Departmental Committee appointed to consider Mr. Rider Haggard's report on agriculatural settlements in British Colonies, 1906. Cd. 2978.
  - V.10-4 Report of the Vagrancy Committee, 1903; 9 (Reel 7)
    Lincolnshire. Parts of Lindsey. Report of the Vagrancy Committee ... 1903.
  - V.10-5 Report to the Local Government Board, 1904; 10 (Reel 7)
    United Kingdom. Report to the ... Local Government Board on methods of dealing with vagrancy in Switzerland: by H. Preston - Thomas, 1904, Cd.2235.
  - V.10-6 A bill to amend the Vagrancy Act, 1824, 1904; 11 (Reel 7)
    United Kingdom. Vagrancy Bill. A bill to amend the Vagrancy Act, 1824, and to facilitate the establishment of Labour Colonies ... 1904. [Bill 124]
- London: Central (Unemployed Body of London, Minutes, 1905-1906 (V.11. ). Same, 1906-1907. (V.12.) (Reel 8)
  - V.11. Minutes of proceedings, 1905-1906; 1 (Reel 8)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Minutes of proceedings from 23rd November, 1905 to 16th November, 1906. Vol I, and Index.
  - V.12. Minutes of proceedings, 1906-1907; 2 (Reel 8)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Minutes of proceedings from 7th December, 1906 to 15th November, 1907. Vol. II, and Index.
- London: Central (Unemployed Body of London, Minutes, 1907-1908 (V.13. ). Unemployed, Labour Exchanges, etc., 1887-1914..(V.14. ) (Reel 9)
  - V.13. Minutes of proceedings, 1907-1908; 1 (Reel 9)
    London: Central (Unemployed) Body for London. Minutes of proceedings from 6th December 1907 to 16th October 1908. Vol. III and Index.
  - V.14-1 Return as to the proceedings of Distress Committees in England and Wales, 1906-1914; 2 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Return as to the proceedings of Distress Committees in England and Wales (and of the Central (Unemployed) Body for London) under the Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905, during the years ended March: - 1906 (1907 = 392). 1907 (1907 = 326). 1908 (1908 = 173). 1909 (1909 = 276). 1910 (1910 = 268). 1911 (1911 = 280). 1912 (1912 = 280). 1913 (1913 = 234). 1914 (1914 = 444).
  - V.14-2 Report by the Local Government Board for Scotland as to the proceedings of Distress Committees, 1906-1913; 3 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Scotland. Unemployed Workmen Act, 1905. Report by the Local Government Board for Scotland as to the proceedings of Distress Committees in Scotland for the years ended May: - 1906 (Cd. 3431). 1907 (Cd. 3830). 1908 (Cd. 4478). 1909 (Cd. 4846). 1910 (Cd. 5409). 1911 (Cd. 5912). 1912 (Cd. 6501). 1913 (Cd. 7127).
  - V.14-3 Return showing in respect of the Common Council of the City of London, 1905; 4 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Unemployed Relief (Work) (London). Return showing in respect of the Common Council of the City of London, and each of the Metropolitan Borough Councils, the amount expended in wages for work undertaken specially for the purpose of providing work for unemployed workmen during the six months ending on the 31st day of March 1905, (etc.).
  - V.14-4 Unemployed Workmen Bill, 1905; 5 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Unemployed Workmen Bill. A Bill to establish organisation with a view to the provision of employment or assistance for Unemployed Workmen in proper cases ... 1905. [Bill 186].
  - V.14-5 Vagrancy Bill, 1904; 6 (Reel 9)
    [United Kingdom. Vagrancy Bill, 1904. See Vol. X, item 6].
  - V.14-6 Labour Exchanges Bill, 1909; 7 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Labour Exchanges Bill. A Bill intituled an Act to provide for the establishment of Labour Exchanges and for other purposes incidental thereto ... 1909. (128).
  - V.14-7 Prevention of Unemployment Bill, 1914; 8 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Prevention of Unemployment Bill. A Bill to establish a Minister of Labour to make provision for the Prevention of Unemployment, to provide for the proper treatment of unemployed person, and for other purposes connected therewith ... 1914. [Bill 127].
  - V.14-8 Miscellaneous papers as to unemployed relief, 1887-1906; 9 (Reel 9)
    Miscellaneous papers as to unemployed relief: a. Home Arts and Industries Association: the unemployed: self-improvement as relief work. 1906. b. Crowder (A.G.). Suggestions for dealing with distress in London caused by lack of employment. c. Mansion House Conference on the Condition of the Unemployed. Sub-Committee on Agricultural Colonies, etc. proposals ... by Herbert V. Mills. 1887. d. Mansion House Conference on the Condition of the Unemployed. Sub-Committee on Agricultural Colonies, etc. proposal for training able-bodied men in country pursuits by means of the Poor Law ... by Samuel A. Barnett. 1887. e. Mansion House Conference on the Condition of the Unemployed. Sub- Committee on Agricultural Colonies, etc. [report on London unemployed in Lincolnshire] ... by Andrew Mearns. 1887. f. Mansion House Council: Report of Reference Committee. 1887. g. Shoreditch. Conference re Unemployed ... December 18th, 1893. Agenda. h. Shoreditch. Vestry of the Parish of Saint Leonard. Special report of the Committee re the Unemployed, with a suggested scheme for government action. 1893. i. Woolwich, Metropolitan Borough of. Report of Conference appointed ... to consider the present and probably future lack of employment in the Borough, and resolutions passed thereon by the Council. 1903.
  - V.14-9 Organisationen der Arbeiter, Gehilfen und Angestellten, 10 (Reel 9)
    Troeltsch (W.). Organisationen der Arbeiter, Gehilfen und Angestellten: die Arbeitslosigkeit in einigen sachverwandten deutschen Industriearbeitenverbander (In Soziale Praxis), I. and II.
  - V.14-10 Copy of report of the Surveyor on the demolition of Millbank Prison by the unemployed, 1893; 11 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Millbank prison. Copy of report of the Surveyor on the demolition of Millbank Prison by the unemployed. 1893. 419.
  - V.14-11 Dock Labour in relation to Poor Law Relief, 1908; 12 (Reel 9)
    United Kingdom. Dock Labour in relation to Poor Law Relief. Report to the ... Local Government Board on dock labour in relation to Poor Law Relief: by ... Gerald Walsh. 1908. Cd. 4391.
  - V.14-12 The only course for poor people to get speedy employment, 13 (Reel 9)
    Robinson (Henry). The Office of addresses and encounters ... or, The only course for poor people to get speedy employment, (etc.). (Copy by Sir William Beveridge).
  - V.14-13 Arbeitsamter und arbeitsstatistische Amter im Ausland., 1914; 14 (Reel 9)
    Germany. Reichs-Arbeitsblatt, Marz 1914. Sonder - Abdruck. Arbeitsamter und arbeitsstatistische Amter im Ausland.
  - V.14-14 Die Aufarbeitung den monatlichen Arbeitsmarktstatistik des Reichs-Arbeitsblatts, 1914; 15 (Reel 9)